http://www.societyofsuccess.com/members/privacy-policy

×
Some text in the Modal..
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY:
Welcome to the NSLS Privacy Center - take a look around. You'll learn how the NSLS treats your personal information, along with ways to control your preferences and settings.The National Society of Leadership and Success (the "NSLS") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will handle your personal information carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy describes how the internet website owned and operated by The National Society of Leadership and Success, LLC, a New Jersey limited liability company (the "Company") and located at nsls.org (the "Site") collects and uses your personal information in connection with the services and membership benefits we offer through the Site (the "Services"). For purposes of this Privacy Policy, Personal Information shall include any information that identifies you, such as your name, address, phone number, fax number, and email address, as well as any information of a private nature which you provide to us, such as credit card information, financial account information, and Grade Point Average information (collectively "Personal Information"). By visiting the Site, you accept and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
PRIVACY
What information do we collect? While you can visit the Site without providing Personal information, you must submit certain information to register as a Member. Members are those who create and register with a member ID. The NSLS must collect certain information from users in order to customize the Site to meet your individual needs and to tailor the Services to you and your specific Services.
1) Your Personal Information. Personal Information collected from users may include Registration Information, Billing Information, Account Settings, Educational Information and other information you may intentionally share. Each user, including both members and advisors, must create a NSLS account before the Services provided by the NSLS. In order to register, you must provide your name, a member ID, password, email address, date of birth, mobile phone number, permanent home contact information, and educational information (Registration Information). If you make a payment to the NSLS, you must also provide billing information such as a name, address, email address, and financial information corresponding to your selected method of payment (Billing Information). After creating an account, you can then set various preferences and provide additional personal information to pages like Profile. Any data or content you provide when using the Service, such as User Content and responses, will also be collected and stored by the NSLS for your benefit ("User Data"). Finally, we may also collect other information which you intentionally share with us from time to time, such as testimonials and other information. If any of your personal information changes, you may update it at any time.
2) Information Automatically Collected by the Site. Our servers may automatically collect certain aggregated, non-personal identifying information when you visit the Site, such as your computer's IP address, the number of users clicking on a particular link or service, the type of browser in use, the pages viewed, and any external source referring you to the Site (such as a link on another website or in an email). This information is used to understand how visitors navigate the Site in order to enhance your experience when using it. We do not link this information to any information that may personally identify you, nor will we use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information available to any third party, whether for advertising, marketing, or other purposes.
3) Information Collected from Third Parties. We may also collect your Personal Information or other data from third parties if you interact with the NSLS on a third party site. As an example, if you interact with the NSLS using your Facebook® account, the NSLS collects information about your Facebook® account that you agree to share with us at the time you give permission for the NSLS account to be linked to your Facebook® account.
4) Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order to collect information about your activities on the site or to make it easier for you to use certain site functions. The cookie transmits this information back to the site's computer. Many users do not realize that cookies are being placed on their computers when they visit a website. If you want to know when this is happening, or if you want to prevent it from happening, you can set your internet browser to warn you when a website attempts to place a cookie on your computer. The Company does use cookies to manage a user's use of the Site and to analyze in the aggregate the manner in which users use the Site. The sole purpose of the Company's use of cookies is to increase the functionality of the Site and to make the Site as useful as possible for users. No Personal Information shall be gathered or stored in cookies when a user visits the Site.
How do we use your information? We understand that in many situations you want to keep your Registration Information or User Data private. Unless you decide to share User Data with the public, we will not use it for our own purposes, except in the limited circumstances identified in this Privacy Policy or unless we have your express consent. Personal Information will only be used:
To provide you with our services and to customize them to your needs
To facilitate account creation
To monitor and improve our services and features
To analyze your use of the Site and improve the Services
To deliver communications to you relevant to your use of the Services
To fulfill your requests for products and membership benefits
To enforce the Company's Terms and Conditions of Use
To prevent potentially illegal activities
To screen for undesirable or abusive activity
To create new services, features or content
When Might We Disclose your User Data or Personal Information to Third Parties? We will only share your User Data and other Personal Information with third parties in limited situations, and only after we have done one of three things, in accordance with applicable law (a) given you notice, such as in this Privacy Policy, (b) obtained your express consent, or (c) anonymized the information so that it does not identify the individual. In accordance with the above, we may disclose your User Data or other Personal Information as follows:
To our service providers, to provide the Services
To your billing contact, if your (account holder's) details are different than the billing contact listed for your account
To third parties as anonymous, aggregated information, to improve and promote our Services
If required to do so by law
In connection with the merger, sale or acquisition of the Company, to the other party in connection with such transfer
Information you expressly consent to be shared
To our affiliate partners listed on the "Partners" section of the Site
5) Retargeting. As you browse nsls.org, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand your interests. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with nsls.org. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll's and their partners' targeted advertising.
Our service providers are contractually required to keep your information confidential and to use it only for the purposes of providing their services to us. However, the Company assumes no responsibility for any third party's use of your Personal Information if that information is properly distributed to them in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the Services, you expressly authorize the Company to distribute your Personal Information to these enumerated third parties for the reasons provided herein. You further agree that the use of your Personal Information by these third parties will be governed by their own privacy practices when said information is in their possession, and that the Company will not be liable for any damages which may result from the breach of those third parties' privacy practices.
Your Rights to Your Personal Information. You can update your Personal Information at any time on the account Profile page. It is your responsibility to back up your User Data. You may delete your User Data, but it will not be permanently deleted immediately. To the extent permitted by law, we will permanently delete your data if you request to cancel or delete your account, which you can do by contacting us at help@nsls.org. Deleting your account will cause all User Data in your account to be permanently deleted, as permitted by law, and will disable your access to the Services. We will respond to any requests to access, correct, update or delete your Personal Information within the time period specified by law (if applicable) or without excessive delay. Any requests to delete Personal Information will be promptly fulfilled, unless the request is not technically feasible or such data is required by law to be retained.
How Long is your Information Retained? Generally, your Personal Information is retained for as long as you remain a Member with us, or for as long as is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, or to enforce our agreements. However, data that is deleted from our servers may remain as residual copies on backup servers or other media.
SECURITY
Providing security for the Personal Information you submit on the Site is one of the Company's top priorities, and it takes commercially reasonable measures to protect against the unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of such information. Users are required to create a unique member ID and password that must be entered each time a user logs on to the Site. Session cookies are then issued only to record encrypted authentication information for the duration of the user's specific session. The session cookies do not include the user's username or password.
When a user accesses secured areas of the Site, Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology protects their information using both server authentication and data encryption to ensure that data is safe, secure, and only available to authorized users. All passwords and credit card information are transferred via encrypted SSL connections, as are all postings made by Users. Your User Data and User Content are treated as the private property of the User, subject to a limited license for use by the NSLS. The Company does not sell or use such information for its own purposes, except as required by law.
It is important to understand that the security precautions taken by the Company apply only to the Site, and that the Company exercises no control over how your information is stored or maintained by third party sites. Also be aware that, while all appropriate measures are taken by the Company to ensure the safety and security of the information you submit via the Site, no guarantee can be made that information transmitted via the Internet will be entirely secure. Caution should always be used when submitting personal information online. The Company takes commercially reasonable steps to provide security for your information once it has received it.
While the Company takes reasonable steps to prevent others from guessing your password, it is also recommended that you change your password periodically. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your member ID and password and should not provide this information to any third party. The Company is not responsible for any damages incurred if a third party accesses your account through information it received from you or otherwise by reason of your violation of this Privacy Policy or the Site's Terms and Conditions.
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and the Services only. The Site may include links to other websites, including, but not limited to Partner websites, whose privacy practices may differ from those of the Company. If you choose to use the products or services found on these other sites, disclose information to those providers, or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your Personal Information is governed by their privacy practices. You should evaluate the practices of other websites linked to this Site before deciding to use their products or services. The Company's Privacy Policy does not apply to information you may submit to other websites, and the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. The Company may present links in a format that enables it to track whether the links have been followed and whether any action has been taken on third party websites. This information is used only to improve the quality of the Services and to customize the content of the Services.
POSTING CONTENT TO THE SITE
Certain areas of the Site allow users to post User Content which can be seen by other users. If you post any content to the Site, any information submitted can be read, collected or used by other users and can possibly be used to send unsolicited messages to you. The Company is not responsible for the Personal Information you voluntarily choose to post to the Site.
SURVEYS
From time to time, the Company may ask for your participation in surveys designed to improve the Site. Your participation in such surveys is completely voluntarily. Any Personal Information you provide to the Company in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and will otherwise be governed by this Privacy Policy.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
At the NSLS, maintaining our users' privacy and security is always a priority. To this end, we regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges. As such, the NSLS reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If the Privacy Policy is changed in any manner that affects the personally identifying information the Company has collected through the Site, those changes will be posted on the Site and you will be advised of any choices you may have as a result of those changes. For any changes to this Privacy Policy for which you are required to provide prior consent, we will provide you with reasonable notice of such changes before they become effective and provide you with the opportunity to consent to those changes. If you do not cancel your account and continue to use the Services beyond the advance-notice period, you will considered as having expressly consented to the changes in our Privacy Policy. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top by its effective date. All changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. If you disagree with the terms of this Privacy Policy or any updated privacy policy, you may close your account at any time.
SAFETY OF MINORS
The Services are not intended for and may not be used by minors. A "minor" is defined as an individual under the age of majority in his/her place of residence (under age 13 in the United States). The Company does not knowingly collect personal data from minors or allow them to register for an account. If it comes to the Company's attention that information has been collected from a minor or that a minor has registered an account, such data and account will be deleted without notice. If you have reason to believe that this has occurred, please contact us at help@nsls.org.
ENGLISH VERSION CONTROLS
If a non-English version of this Privacy Policy is provided for convenience, the English version shall control and is authoritative in the event of any ambiguity or conflict among translations.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at help@nsls.org, or write to us at the following address: The National Society of Leadership and Success, 1 Evertrust Plaza, Suite 101 Jersey City, NJ 07302. If you submit personal information to us when sending questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or the Site, we will use that information to respond to your correspondence, but will not share it with any third party without your express permission.
The National Society of Leadership and Success
Careers at NSLS
NSLS Foundation
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Blog
1 Evertrust Plaza, Suite 101 Jersey City, NJ 07302
Enter your nomination code.
Submit
Don’t have a code?
×
